Okay, then I got to ask you about the
Fibonacci line.
>> [music]
>> Was it intentional that five, two, and
three are Fibonacci numbers, but in the
wrong order?
I was saying If you listen to my music,
I flip stuff all the time. I always say
it one way and I'll say it back. Carl
Lewis, Lewis and Clark, yeah, yeah.
With the Fibonacci, I was like,
somebody's going to catch this. Somebody
knows it's going to
It's the golden rule or something like
that. I always [snorts] mess it up.
mean, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's
[clears throat] intentional everyone out
there. It's an intentional thing.
>> [laughter]
>> It's intentional. I know. That's what
I'm saying, man. I'm such a jittery
person as you probably think, but the
fact that you caught little stuff like
that, it just means like I'm I'm doing
it right.